[
   {
      "sQuestion":"From which did the COVID originate ?",
      "sAnswer":"Wuhan",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "Wuhan",
         "Beijing",
         "Fuyang"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"what is the name for the new CoronaVirus disease reported on 31st Dec 2019 to WHO ?",
      "sAnswer":"COVID19",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "COVID19",
         "COVID20",
         "COVID18"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"COVID19 virus will not spread by ?",
      "sAnswer":"Social Distancing",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "Social Distancing",
         "coughing",
         "Close Contact"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"General Incubation period of COVID19 ?",
      "sAnswer":"range of 1-14 days",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "range of 1-14 days",
         "range of 1-20 days",
         "range of 1-70 days"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"Which of the following is not complication of COVID19 ?",
      "sAnswer":"Heart-Attack",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "Pneumonia",
         "Heart-Attack",
         "Kidney failure"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"Which of the following is not preventive measure for avoiding COVID19 ?",
      "sAnswer":"Hugging",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "Hugging",
         "Hand wash",
         "Quarantine"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"Which country has More COVID case as of May ?",
      "sAnswer":"USA",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "USA",
         "INDIA",
         "CHINA"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"what does COVID stands for ?",
      "sAnswer":"Corona Virus Disease",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "Corona Virus Disease",
         "Combo virus Disease",
         "Corona Virtual Disease"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"can people recover from COVID19 ?",
      "sAnswer":"Yes",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "Yes",
         "No",
         "Maybe"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"who names COVID19 ?",
      "sAnswer":"WHO",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "WHO",
         "CHINA",
         "USA"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"what was the first name of new coron virsu found on December 2019 ?",
      "sAnswer":"2019-nCoV",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "SARS-CoV-2",
         "2019-nCoV",
         "SARS-CoV"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"When you go for market you should wear following to avoid COVID19 spread ?",
      "sAnswer":"Mask",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "Shoes",
         "Watches",
         "Mask"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"In which country COVID19 case was initially found ?",
      "sAnswer":"CHINA",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "USA",
         "CHINA",
         "ITALY"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"Following method you have to follow when you are in public places to prevent contracting COVID-19 ?",
      "sAnswer":"Social Distancing",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "Social Distancing",
         "shaking hand",
         "hugging"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"Following preventive measure you have to follow when you touch items outside ?",
      "sAnswer":"wash hand with sanitizer",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "wash hand with sanitizer",
         "touch face with hand",
         "touch face with eye"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"Pick the right statement from following",
      "sAnswer":"Most people who get COVID19 will recover from it",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "people who get COVID19 will die",
         "Most people who get COVID19 will recover from it",
         "people who get COVID19 will suffer lifelong"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   },
   {
      "sQuestion":"use of Hand driers will kill COVID19 Virus ?",
      "sAnswer":"yes",
      "sMultiOptions":[
         "yes",
         "no",
         "maybe"
      ],
      "iHitCounter":0
   }
]